Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series II. Manuscripts
  - Watsonville: drafts 1994 Nov. 27 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1995 Feb. 25 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1995 Mar. 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Watsonville: drafts for Fund for N.A.P. 1995 Mar. 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Watsonville: drafts changes-in-progress for reading 1995 May 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1995 May 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Watsonville: drafts-in-progress, with notes 1995 May 9 -June 6 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Bardacke, Frank [computer file: Moraga/INTERVIEWS copy/Bardacke, Frank+] n.d [c. 1994] (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Betancourt, Gloria n.d (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Carvajal, Ricardo 1994 Sept. 6 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Contreras, Esperanza 1994 Sept. 5 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Contreras, Esperanza n.d. [c. 1994] (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Contreras, Esperanza n.d. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Donnely, Eileen and Rosie Chavez n.d. [c. 1994] (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Garcia, Barbara 1994 May 19 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Gomez, Cruz 1994 June 16 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Guillermina & Ricardo n.d. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Guzman, Reyna 1994 Aug. 23 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Lerma, Lydia 1994 Aug. 9 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Medina, Luisa [1 of 2] 1994 July 29 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Medina, Luisa [2 of 2] 1994 July 29 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Miller, Mike, Fr. 1994 Aug. 19 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Moreno, Chavelo 1994 June (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Moreno, Chavelo n.d. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- Rodriguez, Guillermina 1994 Aug. 28 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- "Watsonville on Strike" video (English version) n.d. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Watsonville: interviews -- "Watsonville on Strike" video (Spanish version) n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Watsonville: interviews [print-outs from computer disks] [1 of 2] n. d. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Watsonville: notas and research on border and immigration 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Watsonville: notas and research on resources c. 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Watsonville: notas and research on business 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Watsonville: notas and research on Irene Lara's papers 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - What we're rollin around in bed with: sexual silences in Feminism [with Amber Hollibaugh]. reprint n.d. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Women's weekend c. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Words n.d. [c. 1970s] (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ya vas, carnal: poetry by Rodrigo Reyes, Francisco X. Alarcón, & Juan Pablo Gutierrez, Review of n.d. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous poems -- 1973-1974 1973 -1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous poems and prose -- late 1970s 1970s (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous poems and prose -- early '80s [A - M] 1980s (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous poems and prose -- early '80s [N - Z]; fragments and miscellaneous 1980s (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous poems and short prose -- late 1980s 1980s (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous fragments and untitled poems -- late 1980s 1980s (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Talks, miscellaneous notes 1991 Feb. 6 -1995 Oct., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous drawings and notes n.d. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - [RESTRICTED] Beach Story '70s [There were always more men than women at nude beaches..."] [1 of 4] c. 1970s (Box 22, Folder 1)
    TMs, 9 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Beach Story '70s [There were always more men than women at nude beaches..."] [2 of 4] c. 1970s (Box 22, Folder 2)
    TMs, 8 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Beach Story '70s [3 of 4] c. 1970s (Box 22, Folder 3)
    TMs, 15 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Beach Story '70s ["A Needle in the Camel's Eye"] [4 of 4] c. 1970s (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["After the game"] 1975 Feb. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    TMs, 1 p.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["An Alternate Route"] 1975 May 24 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Breaking Water ?"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Colonization of My Heart"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    TMs, 5 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["A Composite Portrait"] 1975 Apr. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Conversation"] 1976 Mar. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["A Conversation Between Dreams"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    TMs, 2 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Diagram"] 1975 Apr. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Fire is Dying Down"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    AMs, 3 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["For Joanne"] 1975 Jan. 29 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Hollywood in the thirties view"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    AMs, 2 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["I am nostalgic for you..."] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["I am sleeping alone again tonight"] 1975 May -1978 June (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["I flop onto the toilet at seven a.m."] 1977 Dec. 1 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["I spent an entire afternoon"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    AMs, 1 p.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["In Answer To Your Question / or The Filing System in My Mind"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["In Answer To Your Question / or The Filing System in My Mind"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["It has taken us a long time to cut things down to size"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["John Says"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Just Between You and Me"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    TMs with handwritten annotations, 1 p.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Lady Cowboy"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Listen"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Melodrama of the Diaphram [sic]"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Mime"] 1975 Apr. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    TMs (reprint), 1 p.
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Mousetrap"] 1975 Feb. 10 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Muscle Woman"] 1975 Spring (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["My Obsession" with fragment] 1975 May 12 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["My Therapist says, 'Its an existential fear'"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Nothing to hold mine"] 1975 Mar. 3 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["On Woodlake Inn Stationary" and "Water Poem"] 1975 May -1976 Mar. (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Oregon Creek"] 1975 Summer (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Our last trip"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Paranoia"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["A Poem about glaciers and weak knees"] 1979 Apr. 6 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Returning from the Airport for the One Hundreth [sic] Time"] 1975 Oct. (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Roomates: A Portrait of two women"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["The Slip"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Three or Thirteen Years Later"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Venice Church Bells / Outside this house estranged"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Water resettles with no memory of disturbance;"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["We saw nothing of eachother [sic]"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Womb Women"] 1975 June 4 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - [RESTRICTED] Poems, drafts, 1977 and earlier ["Your Style of Covert Revisitation"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 47)
    TMs with handwritten annotations, 2 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["I am a hairy woman..."] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["I could describe the wind..."] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["The early evening chill"] 1973 Nov. 7 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["I began by describing to Bill..."] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["More Pieces"] 1976 Nov. 10 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    TMs, 3 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["The orange sun has slipped down..."] 1974 Spring (Box 22, Folder 53)
    TMs with handwritten annotations, 15 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Reflections of a teacher"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Sister Verona's frog clicked..."] 1973 Nov. 29 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    TMs, 4 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["The Stone Cherub"] 1973 Spring (Box 22, Folder 56)
    TMs, 13 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Story-in-Progress"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 57)
    TMs, 7 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Throughout the day as I passed..."] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Two Weekends"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["Two Weekends"] n.d. (Box 22, Folder 60)
    TMs, 10 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Prose - L.A. and College ["A Wednesday night and all I have..."] 1976 Oct. 27 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- Series III. Journals
  - Journal: "Memories, Dreams and Reflections" c. 1972 -1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journal: May 1975 - August 1975 1975 May 7 -Aug. 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Journal: September 1975 - November 1976 1975 Sept. 15 -1976 Nov. 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Journal: "Travel - Dec. 75 / Apr. - Jun 76" December 1976 - June 1977 1975 Dec. 26 -1977 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journal: "Fall 1977 Berkeley, California" July 1977 - February 78 1977 July -1978 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journal / Notes c. 1978 -1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journal: March 78 - January 1979 1978 Mar. 15 -1979 Jan. 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Journal: "On Adrienne Rich" Notebook 8/24/79 - 10/29/79 1979 Aug. 24 -Oct. 29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Journal: Sept. 1979 - March 1980 1979 Sept. -1980 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Journal: March 1980 - October 1980 1980 Mar. -Oct. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Journal: October 1980 - July 1981 1980 Oct. -1981 July (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Journal: July 1981 - February 1982 1981 July -1982 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Journal: Febrero a Mayo, 1982 1982 Feb. -May (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Journal: May - July 1982 1982 May -July (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Journal: July - September 1982 / Oct. 1982 July -Oct. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Journal: September 1982 - April 1983 1982 Sept. -1983 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Journal: Ogosto 1983 - Octubre 1983 1983 Aug. -Oct. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Journal: Noviembre 1983 - Marzo 1984 1983 Nov. -1984 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Journal: Marzo -Junio 84 1984 Mar. -June (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Journal / Notes 1984 Mar. -1985 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Journal: June 84 - January 85 1984 June -1985 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Journal: Jan - March 1985 1985 Jan. -Mar. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Journal: 85 septiembre - 86 enero 1985 Sept. 7 -1986 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Personal Writings: Theater Notes; Script Analysis, The Jean Shelton Acting School 1985 -1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Journal: Enero - Junio 1986 1986 Feb. 23 -June (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Journal / Notes 1986 June -July (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Personal Writings: "librito del camino y regreso" 1986 June -July (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Journal: 18 julio1986 - 6 enero 1987 1986 July 18 -1987 Feb. 6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Personal Writings: "It is the worst time for me to be writing..." 1986 Aug. 18 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Personal Writings: "Papeles de huerfana" 1986 Oct. 19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Personal Writings: "Corazón del cielo" 1987 Feb. 21 -Nov. 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Personal Writings: "Work on what has been spoiled" November 1987 - 4 Marzo 1988 1987 Nov. -1988 Mar. 4 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Journal: March 6, 1988 - 7 julio 1988 1988 Mar. 6 -1988 July 7 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Journal: 16 ogosto 1988 - Nov. 1, 1988 1988 Aug. 16 -1988 Nov. 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Journal: Oct. 1988 - May 1989 1988 Oct. -1989 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Journal: Nov. 2, 1988 - 17 Mayo 1989 1988 Nov. 2 -1989 May 17 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Journal: May 27, 1989 - 29 Julio 1989 1989 May 27 -1989 July 29 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Journal: August 1989 and Mexico trip; "Xmas", 1989 1989 Aug. -1989 Dec. 25 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Journal (includes "Heroes and Saints" notes; Early hits of "Media"): 30 ogosto 1989 - 28 enero 1990 1989 Aug. 30 -1990 Feb. 28 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Journal("beginning notas" of "Art in America" and "Queer Aztlan"): 16 January 1990 - June 3, 1990 1990 Jan. 16 -1990 June 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Journal: 11 Julio 1990 - 10 Feb. 1991 1990 July 11 -1991 Feb. 10 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Personal writings: "Notes throughout my Mexican travels - Mexico: La Jornada"; 1990 - 1991 1990 -1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Playwriting/speech notes"; "Heroes Development; "First Notes toward Queer Aztlan": Feb. - March 1991 1991 Feb. -1991 Mar. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Journal ("First notes to: 'La Fuerza Femenina'; Earliest 'Medea' Notes"): 16 marzo 1991 - 2 sept. 1991 1991 Mar. 16 -1991 Sept. 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Journal ("Mexico"): 17 Mayo 1991 - 12 Julio 1991 1991 May 17 -1991 July 12 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Eclipse 91/ LA Rep Conferencia Notes; Empezando en Zihuatanejo, Mexico": 28 junio 1991 1991 June 28 -1991 July 12 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Journal: 17 Sept. 1991 - 28 Feb. 1992 1991 Sept. 17 -1992 Feb. 28 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Journal ("Chicano Codices Notes"): February 1992 - July 10, 1992 1992 Feb. -1992 July 10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Early Bicultural Mind Writings" July 17 - Oct. 29 1992 1992 July 17 -Oct. 29 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Journal ("Tejas Trip; "Last Generation Notas"): November 1992 1992 Nov. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Journal ("More Bicultural Mind Notes; "Popol Vuh"; "Waiting in the Wings"; "Queer Aztlan": Dec. 1, 1992 - 13 marzo 1993 1992 Dec. 1 -1993 Mar. 13 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Waiting in the Wings"; "Popol Vuh"; "Andre Essay": March 19 - July 20, 1993 1993 Mar. 19 -1993 July 20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Nurses Addresses": July 93 - Nov. 93 1993 July -Nov. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Waiting in the Wings" :July 25. 1993 - Feb. 28. 1994 1993 July 25 -1994 Feb. 28 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Waiting in the Wings"; "Early Watsonville": 16 marzo 94 - 12 nov. 94 1994 Mar. 16 -Nov. 12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Watsonville"; "Medea": Nov. 14, 1994 - Jan. 23, 1995 1994 Nov. 14 -1995 Jan. 23 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Notebook/Agenda n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Notebook/ Agenda n. d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - notebook: addresses, agenda n. d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - address notebook n. d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - address notebook n. d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - address notebook n. d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - Subseries a. Personal
    - Aguilar, Marcella 1994 Apr. 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aguirre, Dolores 1994 Dec. 16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allison, Dorothy 1982 Oct. 15 -1994 Feb. 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alvarez, Julia 1992 Oct. 20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anaya, Rudolfo A. 1983 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Andalzúa, Gloria 1981 Jan. 11-Nov. 22 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Andalzúa, Gloria 1982 Jan. 9 -1987 Sept. 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Baiz, Ana 1989 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bridgforth, Sharon 1991 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Cantú, Norma 1991 Jan. 18 -1994 Aug. 22 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Castaniero, Richard n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Castillo, Ana 1988 Nov. -1989 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Castillo, Ana 1988 Nov. -1989 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Castillo, Ana: misc. greeting cards n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Castillo, Marcel n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Castillo, Rachel Rocha 1987 Jan. 28 -1989 Sept. 26 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chai, Alice 1992 Jan. 9 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chicano Studies Classes 1a & 1b, University of California Berkeley. 1988 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Chai, Alice 1981 Oct. 9 -1985 June (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Claussen, John 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Chrystos n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - DiFarnecio, Doris 1992 Nov. 24 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - DIVAS n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Donnelly, Nisa n.d. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Druid Heights Artists' Retreat, Point Reyes, Ca 1992 Apr. 21 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Facie, Linda 1984 Jan. 30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Freedman, Estelle [Stanford University Program in Feminist Studies] 1994 Nov. 22 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Fried, Philip [The Manhattan Review] 1994 Mar. 2 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - García, Guadalupe 1990 Sept. 23 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Gearhart, Sally 1980 Dec. 8 -1983 Mar. 5, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Grahn, Judy 1979 May 4 -1981 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Grancich, James and Judy 1990 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Haro, Lourdes 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Healy, Eloise Klein 1976 Aug. 9 -1979 Nov. 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Healy, Eloise Klein 1980 Jan. 15 -1984 Jan. 23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Herms, Dieter 1989 July 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Hernandez, Innes 1986 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Hidalgo, Osa 1989 July 13 -1992 Oct. 7 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hollibaugh, Amber 1980 July -1984 Mar. 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Klimek, Martin n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence, Vera and Joe 1988 Apr. 28 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Lorde, Audre [plus book reviews, obituary material from Barbara Smith, and misc.] 1981 July 29 -1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Lutz, H. 1987 Aug. 21 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Martinez, Alma 1993 Apr. 28 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Matthews, Tede [includes Memorial Service and letters, poems, and C. J. Barragan III] 1990 July 8 -1993 Oct. 16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Menchu, Rigorberto 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Teilani Tami J. 1992 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Morales, Aurora [includes mss.] 1980 Aug. 18 -1984 Sept. 6 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Nahm-Mijo, Trina [includes TMS of "Eve"] 1992 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Oceguera, Alma 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - O'Donnell, Brigid n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Palacios, Monica n.d. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - PAPUSA [López, Marua Luisa Molina n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Parreñas, Celine Salazar 1992 Sept. 16 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Pendleton, Karleen 1991 Nov. 23 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Ponce - Jefe, Colonel Emilio 1991 Jan. 30 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Pratt, Minnie Bruce 1991 Nov. 15 -1983 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Quintanales, Mirtha 1980 Dec. 13 -1982 Oct. 15 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Quintanales, Mirtha 1983 Mar. 28 -1986 Feb. 11, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Ramirez, Belinda 1989 May (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Ramos, Linda 1995 Jan. 19 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ramos, Yolanda 1993 July 29 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Rawles, Nancy 1984 July 7 -Dec. 11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Rawles, Nancy 1985 Jan. 20 -Apr. 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Reid, Barbara 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Revlech, Diana 1986 Oct. 15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Rice - Trujillo, Maya 1995 Jan. 31 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Ruiz, Sandra 1990 May 18 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Rich, Adrienne 1979 Mar. 3 -1982 Nov. 4, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Romero, Lora 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Romero, Rolando J. 1994 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ruano, Monserrat Borrego n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Saeta, Elsa [University of Texas - Pan American] 1993 May (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Salinas, Raúl [including East of the Freeway: Reflections de mi pueblo and "About invasion and conquest"] [1992] 1994 Nov. 7 -1995 May (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Sánchez, Elba [includes Cherríe Moraga's "What I am"] 1994 Sept. 21 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Sarigliano, Marta E. [includes: El Santuario de Chimayo] 1991 Oct. -1992 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Sequeria, Lupita [1 of 2] 1990 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Sequeria, Lupita [2 of 2] 1990 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Serrano, Irma n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Barbara: early letters and articles 1979 -1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Som, Indigo 1994 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Stephens, Renée 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Tejana, Merienda 1985 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Telushkin, Rachel 1993 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Yamato, Gloria 1990 Dec. 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Yrigoyen, Chabela 1981 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Zendejas, Rosalie n.d. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified n.d. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified n.d. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Subseries b. Business
    - American Writers Congress [correspondence regarding Arthur Bell] 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Arellanes, Lisa [Brava! for Women in the Arts] 1994 Aug. 31 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Arrellano, Cathy [personal assistant to Cherríe Moraga] [ Miscellaneous notes] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Arts Democratic Club [Axel, Rachelle] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Badikian, Beatriz [Fem] 1983 Aug. 8 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Barnard College [Schenck, Celeste M.] [poetry competition request] 1990 Dec. 15 -1991 Dec. 11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Barrera, Vivian Otero n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bennett, Suzanne [Peterson, Jane T.] 1993 Dec. 7 -1994 Feb. 21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bogatin, M. J. [attorney for Cherríe Moraga] 1993 Sept. 29 -1994 Feb. 18 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bogatin, M. J. [attorney for Cherríe Moraga] 1994 Feb. 22 -Dec. 26 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bustamente, Frank A. n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Carillo, Cameron n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chávez, Denise [Arte Público Press] [re: Shattering the Myth] 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Conditions [Allison, Dorothy, et al.] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Contreras, Angela n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Corinne, Tee A. [The Poetry of Sex: Lesbians write the erotic; contract and contributor list] 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Curby, Dawn n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Deadicated to the one I love n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Dictionary of Hispanic Biography [Chamberlain, Margaret] 1995 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Duke University Press [Negotiating Performance / edited by Diane Taylor and Juan Villegas] 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Fernández, Roberta [re: In other words: literature by Latinas of the United States] 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Five Star Insurance Co. n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Frontiers: a journal of women's studies [Lamphere, Louise] 1991 Jan. -Apr. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Gerbode, Wallace Alexander Foundation [Layton, Thomas C.] 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Goddard College, Plainfield, Vermont [Mitchell, Nora] 1994 May (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Haring-Smith, Tori [re: Monologues by women, for women] 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Hayden, Jeffrey 1991 Jan. 2 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Richard [The Denver Post] 1993 Jan. 20 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Kenyon Review 1991 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 30)